{
    "1": {"question": "Which type of razor has a fixed blade attached to it?", "answer": "A conventional straight razor has a blade that is fixed and cannot be removed."},
    "2": {
    "question": "What is the direction you are cutting called?",
    "answer": "The direction you are cutting with a razor is called the cutting stroke."
    },
    "3": {
    "question": "Where are used blades disposed of?",
    "answer": "Used blades should be disposed of in a sharps container box."
    },
    "4": {
    "question": "What chemical is used to help clot the blood during a blood spill incident?",
    "answer": "Styptic powder, which is made of the astringent alum, is used to help clot the blood during a blood spill incident."
    },
    "5": {
    "question": "What are the 4 different types of cutting strokes?",
    "answer": "There are four types of cutting strokes: freehand, reverse freehand, backhand, and reverse backhand."
    },
    "6": {
    "question": "Shaving against the grain is called what?",
    "answer": "Shaving against the grain is called giving a close shave."
    },
    "7": {
    "question": "What is envisioning?",
    "answer": "Envisioning is a process used before doing a haircut, facial design, flat iron, roller, or rod set."
    },
    "8": {
    "question": "Which facial shape is the normal shape?",
    "answer": "The normal facial shape is the oval shape."
    },
    "9": {
    "question": "What are the different facial shapes?",
    "answer": "There are three main facial shapes: oval, oblong, and round."
    },
    "10": {
    "question": "Why should oblong facial types have hairstyles that are short?",
    "answer": "Oblong facial types should have hairstyles that are short because longer styles will make the face appear longer."
    },
    "11": {
    "question": "Which facial shape is named after a fruit?",
    "answer": "A facial shape with very wide cheekbones and a narrow chin is called an inverted triangle."
    },
    "12": {
    "question": "What areas of the face should you use long strokes?",
    "answer": "Long strokes should be used on the jaw area of the face."
    }
}